<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<layout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    tools:context=".ui.privacy_policy.PrivacyPolicyActivity">

    <data>

        <import type="android.view.View" />

        <variable
            name="viewModel"
            type="com.ullo.ui.privacy_policy.PrivacyPolicyViewModel" />

    </data>

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <com.ullo.view.ToolBar
            android:id="@+id/toolbar"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Privacy Policy"
            app:leftDrawable="@drawable/baseline_navigate_right" />

        <androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:layout_marginStart="13dp"
            android:layout_marginEnd="13dp">

            <LinearLayout
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:orientation="vertical">

                <androidx.appcompat.widget.AppCompatTextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:fontFamily="@font/roboto_regular"
                    android:text="Terms of service are rules by which one must agree to abide in order to use a service. Terms of service can also be merely a disclaimer, especially regarding the use of websites. Often times in the fine text there will be sentences saying that they are not responsible for any lost data, when in fact they are. Terms of service are rules by which one must agree to abide in order to use a service. Terms of service can also be merely a disclaimer, especially regarding the use of websites. Often times in the fine text there will be sentences saying that they are not responsible for any lost data, when in fact they are. Terms of service are rules by which one must agree to abide in order to use a service. Terms of service can also be merely a disclaimer, especially regarding the use of websites. Often times in the fine text there will be sentences saying that they are not responsible for any lost data, when in fact they are. Terms of service are rules by which one must agree to abide in order to use a service. Terms of service can also be merely a disclaimer, especially regarding the use of websites. Often times in the fine text there will be sentences saying that they are not responsible for any lost data, when in fact they are. Terms of service are rules by which one must agree to abide in order to use a service. Terms of service can also be merely a disclaimer, especially regarding the use of websites. Often times in the fine text there will be sentences saying that they are not responsible for any lost data, when in fact they are. Terms of service are rules by which one must agree to abide in order to use a service. Terms of service can also be merely a disclaimer, especially regarding the use of websites. Often times in the fine text there will be sentences saying that they are not responsible for any lost data, when in fact they are. Terms of service are rules by which one must agree to abide in order to use a service. Terms of service can also be merely a disclaimer, especially regarding the use of websites. Often times in the fine text there will be sentences saying that they are not responsible for any lost data, when in fact they are. Terms of service are rules by which one must agree to abide in order to use a service. Terms of service can also be merely a disclaimer, especially regarding the use of websites. Often times in the fine text there will be sentences saying that they are not responsible for any lost data, when in fact they are. Terms of service are rules by which one must agree to abide in order to use a service. Terms of service can also be merely a disclaimer, especially regarding the use of websites. Often times in the fine text there will be sentences saying that they are not responsible for any lost data, when in fact they are."
                    android:textColor="@color/black"
                    android:textSize="14sp" />

            </LinearLayout>
        </androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView>
    </LinearLayout>

</layout>